xpertsociety.com 2017-10-16

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to the website of MQL5.community!

Here you can familiarize yourself with our Privacy Policy regarding any personal information you provide via www.mql5.com. We are committed to safeguarding your personal data and information that you entrust to us via the Internet.

By accessing and using this website, you are deemed to accept and be bound by this Privacy Policy, as well as this website's Terms of Use.

This website is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on this website. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

### 1\. Links to Other Websites#

This Privacy Policy only covers information collected on this website. This website may contain links to other websites which are not owned or controlled by us. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. You should always be aware of this when you leave this website and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of each website you visit which collects personal information.

### 2\. Protection of Personal Information#

Collection of Personal Information. We collect your personal information, including information that you provide when you register on www.mql5.com or associated services available on www.mql5.com, email us or subscribe to our website newsletters. "Personal information" is any data that can be used to uniquely identify a person, such as name, email address, phone number or credit card information.

Use of Personal Information. We use personal information provided to us electronically via our website to, inter alia, register users, administer and improve our website and associated services, to analyze the website statistics and the effectiveness of the terms of use, as well as for other purposes approved by you. We also use your personal information to communicate with you in other ways. For example, if you contact us via the website, we may use your personal information to respond. We may also use personal information to advise you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy.

From time to time, we may offer optional questionnaires and surveys to our users which we use to obtain additional information. Participation in such surveys and subscription lists is completely voluntary so the website user has a choice whether or not to disclose any requested information. In addition to other purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, contact details collected in connection with surveys and questionnaires are used to mail you questionnaire and survey reports, as well as to monitor or improve the effectiveness of, and user satisfaction with, this website.

Disclosure of Personal Information. We hire other companies or work in association with companies that provide services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of communications, hosting this website, delivery of content and services provided by this website, or performing statistical analysis. We may disclose personal information to those service providers in order to permit the efficient delivery of their services but they will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are obliged to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose your personal information in your profile, on forums and comments to publications, it becomes publicly available and can be viewed by other users.

We may also use or disclose personal information about you for other purposes, including cases when we deem it necessary and appropriate in order to comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process, to protect our rights, property, or personal security of our website users or the general public, to enforce our website's Terms of Use or other agreements, to investigate or take actions against illegal or suspected illegal activities, or in relation with a corporate transaction such as a demerger, merger, consolidation, sale of assets, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, or otherwise, as you may consent.

We may disclose the content of communications, messages and emails but we will not post or publish any personal information, and such information will not be shared with any third-party service providers without your consent, except as specified in this Privacy Policy. We will not sell, rent or lease our mailing lists to any third parties.

Access to Personal Information. If at any time after giving your personal information on this website you decide that you do not wish us to hold or use your Personal Information for any purpose, you can remove yourself from www.mql5.com user list by deleting your account or contacting us by email at support@mql5.com.

Children's Privacy. We recognize the importance of protecting the information about children. Our website is directed to the general public and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. If and when age information is requested on our website, the website automatically blocks the receipt of any personal information from any user whose age is specified as being under 13 and rejects further registration of any such user as a website user.

### 3\. Non-Personal Information Policy#

Our Non-Personal Information Practices. We may collect non-personal information about your visit to our website, including pages you have viewed, links you have clicked, as well as other actions related to your use of our website. Additionally, we may collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring website addresses.

Cookies. Cookies are small text files containing a string of numbers and letters that are placed on your hard disk every time you visit a certain webpage. These files allow to identify your browser when you visit the same website again. Cookies can store user settings and other information. You can set your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when you receive a cookie. Please note however that some website features or services may not function properly without cookies. Any data collected in this manner cannot be used to individually identify website users. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

We use cookies to control the use of our website, collect non-personal information about our users, store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save your time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content on your later visits to our website. This information is also used for statistical analysis to tailor content to usage patterns.

Aggregate Data. We may combine personal information we collect from you with personal information provided by other users, in a non-identifiable format, thus creating aggregate data. We plan to analyze aggregate data mainly to identify group trends. We do not link aggregate user data with personal information and aggregate data can therefore not be used to contact or identify you. We will use user names instead of actual names when creating and analyzing aggregate data. For statistical purposes and tracking group trends, anonymous aggregate data may be shared with other companies with which we have relationships.

### 4\. Changes to This Privacy Policy#

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy from time to time in part or in full. We encourage you to check our Privacy Policy from time to time to keep yourselves updated with the measures we take to protect your personal information. To view the latest version of our Privacy Policy, click on the <Privacy Policy> link at the foot of our home page. Often, when changes are made to this Privacy Policy, we also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Privacy Policy but we may not always give other notices of changes. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you thereof by placing a prominent preliminary notice or by directly sending you a notification to the email address associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the website after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

### 5\. Contact Us#

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at support@mql5.com
